{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","address":"15700 E Eight Mile Rd","zipcode":"48205","owner":"FQSR LLC DBA KBP Foods","licenseNumber":"202818","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"3/9/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000E80FE12060BD54C0A0DAC1A492394540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44243","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","inspectionDate":"2018-11-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"6","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"6","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not repaired according to law","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair according to law."},{"inspectionid":"44243","inspectionDate":"11/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42200","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","inspectionDate":"2018-05-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42200","inspectionDate":"5/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-05-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"A designated dressing room/area shall be provided and used."},{"inspectionid":"42200","inspectionDate":"5/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"Throughout","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"42200","inspectionDate":"5/3/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-501.18","violationDescription":"PLUMBING FIXTURES such as HANDWASHING SINKS, toilets, and urinals shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40413","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","inspectionDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"2","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40413","inspectionDate":"10/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"At the Grease build up","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"40413","inspectionDate":"10/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the COLD HOLDING TEMPERATURES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"40413","inspectionDate":"10/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice machine","location":"ICE MACHINE","subLocation":"At the AIR GAP","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-23T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40413","inspectionDate":"10/12/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"38287","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","inspectionDate":"2017-03-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"38287","inspectionDate":"3/17/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"FRYER AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"38287","inspectionDate":"3/17/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Non-food contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"36778","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","inspectionDate":"2016-09-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36778","inspectionDate":"9/14/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36778","inspectionDate":"9/14/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1109","name":"Kentucky Fried Chicken H730207","violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"Inerface surfaces less than 1/2 inch","location":"BACK DOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1109"}}